to do a double crochet stitch you're
going to start with a yarn over
so with your hook in front of the
working yarn tip of the hook facing you
bring your hook below and behind the
working yarn
now stick the hook into the next hole so
it should look like you have four
strands of yarn on the hook
now you're going to yarn over again so
bring the hook below and behind the
working yarn
and pull that yarn through just the
first two loops on the hook
so it should look like you have three
loops on the hook
yarn over again by bringing the hook
below and behind the working yarn
and pull this yarn through just the
first two loops on the hook
so you are left with two loops on the
hook
then yarn over one last time bringing
the hook below and behind the working
yarn
and pull that yarn through all two loops
on the hook so you're left with one loop
on the hook
and you have made a double crochet
stitch